reallocalsearch.com 2016-01-19

# Privacy Policy | reallocalsearch

## Privacy Policy

reallocalsearch ®, Inc. takes consumer privacy seriously. We are committed to following industry standards, best practices and guidelines relating to the use of consumer information and privacy. reallocalsearch recognizes and complies with the self regulatory policies of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). 

This privacy policy is intended to inform consumers about the way reallocalsearch uses and protects the information we collect about customers and users. Information is collected by reallocalsearch through our website www.reallocalsearch.com, through reallocalsearch-owned and operated websites, and across our various Technology Platforms. All use of Inuvo’s products and services, as well as visits to our websites, are subject to this privacy policy. 

The Right to Change This Policy 

reallocalsearch reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

* * *

Information Collection and Use 

We collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) from reallocalsearch websites when you choose to provide it to us via an information request form or contact us email. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to, name, postal address, telephone number, email address, gender, birth date and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on an reallocalsearch website. We use this information to contact you to respond to an inquiry, and in some instances, certain parts of our reallocalsearch websites require requested PII for you to participate in programs and services. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record-keeping purposes and promotional marketing efforts. 

reallocalsearch also collects PII on our websites when you sign up as an Account Holder. Account Holders include both Advertisers and Publishers who have been qualified and approved for access to an reallocalsearch product or service offering, or Consumers who have created an account to access one of our ecommerce websites. Account Holder information collected includes PII necessary to conduct business including, but not limited to, account holder name, phone number, email address, and/or tax ID number. Payments made to and/or from reallocalsearch require the provision of and specified collection of additional PII which may include, but is not limited to, bank account information and credit card numbers. Phone, facsimile, email and/or cell numbers may be used to contact Account Holders as needed. 

All Account Holder information collected is maintained in a password-protected environment. This information is used for client/customer service, media delivery, contact, billing-payables and receivables and/or other reporting purposes. Account Holders may change, update or add additional information about themselves online through our various reallocalsearch web sites. 

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII) via reallocalsearch websites and our various Technology Platforms. Non-PII cannot be used to contact any single person or entity and may include, but is not limited to, IP address, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with other advertiser websites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to the website, your computer’s operating system (e.g., Windows XP), search terms used and other click and browsing behavior. 

reallocalsearch uses Non-PII for internal purposes such as to administer our websites, improve and customize our websites, and to understand and analyze how our websites are being used for marketing purposes. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We use cookies and web beacons to help manage our websites and analyze usage patterns. Cookies are small packets of data stored on a user’s computer that allow sites to recognize the computer when a user revisits a website. Cookies can be used to provide consumer services such as auto login, information delivery and a better understanding of how users interact with the site. These cookies enable sites to customize the site to a user’s needs and interests, so that they can be as valuable and relevant as possible. 

Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. The use of a web beacon allows a website to record that someone has visited a particular webpage, along with additional Non-PII that the website may choose to include with the beacon. 

You are always free to decline cookies. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, erase cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. For more information about cookies and web beacons, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/. 

Public Forums 

reallocalsearch websites make chat rooms, polls, surveys, forums, message boards, blogs commentary and/or news groups available to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your PII through these channels. 

Third-Party Websites 

reallocalsearch websites may contain links to other websites, including Advertiser offers for Publisher participation. Third parties may perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, providing promotional materials to our users, sending email, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. They have access to your personal information only to the extent necessary to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. reallocalsearch is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of such other websites. reallocalsearch encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. reallocalsearch has no control over the use of information by third-party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any PII to those websites. 

* * *

Information Security and Storage 

Storage of PII 

All information collected via information request forms or contact us emails is only used to respond to that inquiry. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record-keeping purposes and promotional marketing efforts. 

All Account Holder information collected is maintained in a password-protected environment. This information is used for client/customer service, media delivery, contact, billing-payables and receivables and/or other reporting purposes. 

Storage of Non-PII 

We maintain Non-PII collected by our technology for up to 180 days. This data includes, but is not limited to, IP address, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with other advertiser websites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to our websites, your computer’s operating system (e.g., Windows XP), search terms used and other click and browsing behavior. 

Security 

reallocalsearch uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of information and treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. 

* * *

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

We do not sell, rent or share PII collected on reallocalsearch websites with non-affiliated third parties without your consent. 

reallocalsearch may share Non-PII collected via our Technology Platforms with third-party service providers whom have contracted with third-party marketing partners, business partners and/or reallocalsearch clients, and as expressly provided for herein. Similarly, we may enhance the Non-PII collected via our Technology Platforms with Non-PII collected from third-party marketing partners, business partners and/or reallocalsearch clients. This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually. 

We may disclose information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. 

Finally, we may transfer information, including any PII collected via reallocalsearch websites, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.
